yotreat.com 2012-12-30

# Yotreat: Privacy Policy

## Yotreat.com Privacy Policy

Our Privacy policy is designed to inform you as to how yotreat.com uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. yotreat.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you take note of the changes. By using the website, you are agreeing to the following terms. If you do not agree with any of these terms, please do not submit information to us throigh any means.

#### How we collect and use your information

To keep record of how the website has been used by users in different locations, we log users’ IP addresses, drop cookies, track pages views, downloads, etc. We gather details in the form of username, password, date of birth and email address of the users, when they plan to register with us. yotreat doesn’t allow persons who fall under 13 years of age to get registered with us and participate in any of the events of the website. The information provided by users will be used to communicate with them in the form of newsletters, requests, greetings etc. The users’ personal information will not be shared with any third parties.

#### IP address, Cookies, and Web Beacons 

With the help of cookies, Web beacons or new technologies, we store information from your internet browser. It helps to measure the effectiveness of advertisements provided and to enhance the communication with the user. Cookie is a piece of information, which includes a username, the current date and time, stored on the local computer of a person. It helps to access information of visiting frequencies.

#### Third Parties and Sponsors

We may use third party advertising companies to serve different kind of ads when you use our website. These third party advertising companies may use users’ non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser type, available software and hardware information to serve targeted ads about products, services and for measuring ad effectiveness.

#### Third Party Cookies

While providing advertisements for you in this website, our third party advertisers might drop a cookie on your web browser to track the effectiveness of the advertisement.

2012 Yotreat.com: Free Online Games. All Games are copyright of respective owners or authors.
